# （美人鱼烧烤浴盆）
(Mermaid barbecue bathtub)
# 最近有个小兄弟来找我
A bro came to me recently
# 说是想要出去摆摊创业卖烧烤
He said he wanted to set up a market stall and sell barbecue
# 但是现在竞争比较激烈啊
But competitions are intense now
# 最近又是三伏天了
And it’s been a hot season recently
# 烤串比较怕热
Making barbecue can be very hot
# 问我有没有办法解决
So he asked if I had a solution
# 啊，想了一段时间之后
After thinking about it for a while
# 我决定给他做一个美人鱼烧烤浴盆
I decided to make a mermaid barbecue bathtub for him
# (人鱼烧烤)
Mermaid Barbecue
# 给大家介绍一下我的这个美人鱼烧烤浴盆
Let me introduce my mermaid barbecue bathtub
# 等我们出去摆摊儿啊
When we go out and set up a stall
# 卖烧烤的时候
and sell barbecue
# 首先先掀开上面这个盖子
First, open the lid
# 它就会变成一个给我们招揽生意的灯箱
It will become a light box for us to attract business
# 这里是开关
Here is the switch
# 可能是白天的原因啊
Maybe because it’s in the daytime
# 显得不是特别亮
It doesn't seem very bright
# 晚上说咱们的拍拍看
We'll take a look again at night
# 不仅如此，它还可以啊旋转
Besides, it can rotate
# 漂不漂亮
Isn’t it beautiful?
# 下面是一个音乐喷泉
Below is a musical fountain
# 打开开关之后
After the switches are on
# 它就会喷出水来
It's going to spray water
# 而且如果说有音乐的话
And if there is music
# 它还会随着音乐的节拍
It will follow the beat of the music
# 上下起伏
Up and down
# [Music]
# 啊，这个浴池的两边
On both sides of the bath
# 是一个它的烤箱
are the grills
# 打开之后这里可以变成一个小吧台
It can be turned into a small counter when opened
# 我们在里面烧烤的时候不会感觉到炎热
We don't feel hot when we barbecue inside
# 啊如果说水太凉的话你还会感觉到特别冷
You will even feel very cold if the water is too cold
# 但是也不用担心
But no need to worry
# 它在下面有一个啊加热系统
It has a heating system below
# 只需要打开这里
You only need to open here
# 往里面添一些柴火
Add some firewood
# 就可以给浴池加热
Then you can heat the bathtub
# 现在是已经开了，我们可以到里面烧烤了
Now that the water is boiling, we can go inside to barbecue
# 啊，其实里面的水并没有开
Ah, the water is not really boiling
# 只不过是为了视觉效果
This is just for the visual effect
# 我在这个浴池底下安装几个出气孔
I installed some vent holes under this bathtub
# 这里是开关
Here is the switch
# 关上之后，它就没有了
The bubbles disappear after you turn it off
# 然后再打开
Then turn it on again
# 0:04:30.565, 0:04:34.045
# 这个烟是里面有一个雾化器
# The smoke is due to a nebulizer inside
# 可以制造出烟雾来
which can produce mist
# 让我们有一种仙气飘飘的感觉
and let us feel as in the fairyland
# 浴盆尾部的这三个罐子
There are three jars at the end of the bathtub
# 我们可以卖一些可乐啤酒之类的饮料
We can sell drinks like coke and beer
# 里面还有一个美人鱼的套装
There is also a mermaid suit in it
# 下面我穿上整体给大家演示一下
Now I'll put it on to show you
# 穿上这个美人鱼套装之后啊
After putting on the mermaid suit
# 我就会变成一个美人鱼烧烤大师
I will become a mermaid barbecue master
# 让我在激烈的竞争者之中脱颖而出
which lets me stand out from the fierce competition
# 弄不好半条街的烧烤生意都是我的
Perhaps half of the barbecue business on this street will be mine
# 如果能找到一个好看的美人鱼烧烤师啊
If we can find a beautiful mermaid barbecue master
# 生意会更好
The business can be better
# 像我这样的可能会差一点
Having someone like me, the business may not be as good
# 感谢收看，欢迎订阅 – 手工耿
Thank you for watching. Welcome to subscribe. – Handy Geng